

Address 14-6-602 Zhuhuali Community, Huayuanxincheng Nankai District, Tianjin, China

BoyangYan

Personal Evaluation

I see myself advancing with a strong ability and interesting in new technology and academic research. I successfully participated two international academic conferences, one published paper and one patent. In the University study, I got undergraduate scholarships and the best prize for final project. The final project is related to swipe card system. I would like the chance to take specific field of Computer Science to prepare myself for other roles in the Domain. I want to build my new academic experience with UVIC education and training.

Working Experience

2020.3 - now Support Engineer

Microsoft, China

Contact Info

Tel: +86 18512290791

yanboyang713

yanboyang713@

Azure Machine Learning CSS Team

Wechat: 2018.12 - 2020.3 Algorithm Engineer

Peng Chen Laboratory, China

Network Communication Research Center

Mail

gmail.com

boyangy3@ illinois.edu

2018.1 - 2018.11 Research Assistant (Computer Science)

University of Wollongong, Australia

Metamorphic Testing - Software Testing

Education

Web & Git

20

2019.3 - now **Netmath**

University of Illinois (Urbana-Champaign)

University of Wollongong, Australia

github.com/yanboyang713 researchgate.net

Major in Mathematics

Main subjects:

Algebra A+

Preparation for Calculus A+

Programming



OS Preference
GNU/Linux *****
Unix *****
MacOS *****

Windows ★★★★

2014.3 - 2017.12 **Bachelor of Computer Science**

Major in Software Engineering

Main subjects

Algorithms and Data Structures (80 Distinction)

Object and Generic Programming in C++ (75 Distinction)

Interactive Computer Graphics (75 Distinction)

Multimedia Computing (73 Credit)

software Engineering Practices & Principles (82 Distinction)

Main Achievement:

- 1. The best final project prize (Human Research Management System base on Web)
- 2. First Three Semester had: Undergraduate Excellence Scholarship

2013.3 - 2014.3 English for Tertiary Studies

University of Wollongong College, Australia

Main subjects: Academic English

2011.9 - 2013.3 Bachelor of Business Management

China University Of Mining And Technology

Average mark of 91%. Most of courses got High Distinction



Publications

Boyang Yan, Brian Yecies, Zhi Quan Zhou: Metamorphic Relations for Data Validation: A Case Study of Translated Text Messages. IEEE/ACM 4th International Workshop on Metamorphic Testing (MET '19), in conjunction with the 41st International Conference on Software Engineering (ICSE '19), Montreal, Canada; 05/2019

Patents

June 2, 2020 An automated text difference analysis and verification system/method
China Patent Office Application ID: 202010489931.8

Academy Congress and Conference

May 26, 2019

Paper Presentation - Title: Metamorphic Relations for Data Validation:

A Case Study of Translated Text Messages ICSE, Montreal, Canada

August 11, 2017 showing my final year project about Human Resource Management System based on Web (whole swap card subsystem and database are finish independently)

IEEE Sections Congress (SC2017), Sydney, Australia

Certifications

2019 First Aid CPR AED

American Heart Association

2017 Amateur Radio Operator's certificate of proficiency (Standard)

The Wireless Institute of Australia (WIA)

2016 Ross a. Hull memorial Vhf-Uhf contest

The Wireless Institute of Australia (WIA)

Twelfth Place in Section A (Analog Modes, Best 7 Days) and Twelfth Place in Section C (Analog Modes, Best 2 Days)

2014 Amateur Radio Operator's certificate of proficiency (Foundation)

The Wireless Institute of Australia (WIA)

2010 The Second Place Prize Awarded, Tianjin School Sports Competition Award "92" National Games Tianjin

Tianjin Basketball Tryouts, China

High school men's Group B. Primary and Secondary (Vocational) School Basketball Games. Have got the second grading certificate and title